{
  "decks": [
    {
      "name": "AEW Wrestling Trivia",
      "description": "Are you an All Elite Super-Fan? Test your knowledge of All Elite Wrestling",
      "id": 1
    },
    {
      "name": "test",
      "description": "to test study function with too dew cards",
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "name": "trial",
      "description": "deck",
      "id": 3
    }
  ],
  "cards": [
    {
      "front": "Who won the first ever AEW Dynamite match?",
      "back": "Cody Rhodes",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "On the October 16th episode of Dynamite, Chris Jericho debuted which alter ego in AEW?",
      "back": "The Painmaker",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "front": "What is SCUs finishing maneuver?",
      "back": "S-C-U-Later",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 3
    },
    {
      "front": "What is the name of \"Hangman\" Adam Page's entrance music?",
      "back": "Ghost Town Triumph",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "front": "this",
      "back": "that and the other thing",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 6
    },
    {
      "front": "I need",
      "back": "the form to reset",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 7
    },
    {
      "front": "how about",
      "back": "this",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 8
    },
    {
      "front": "how about",
      "back": "this",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 9
    },
    {
      "front": "success",
      "back": "!!",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 10
    },
    {
      "front": "hello",
      "back": "from the other side",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 11
    },
    {
      "front": "only",
      "back": "one card",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 12
    }
  ]
}